Today I'm going to teach you the most ninja way to sell.
Uncle,
About to check out again and you know what i'm Talking About
Just Let me know if you wanna GO.
Oh the man over there,
oh.
And today if you're thinking that we're going to sell this product,
you made a mistake.
Uncle,
pick up on the idea.
Charlie Brown Junior Skateboard Wheel
brownie
I hope you like it here,
o edible skateboarding people.
Cidade Santos tamo together valeu is us bora there for the bora track
that now we will arrive in the strong skateboarding crowd.
Only if you'll be happy if you don't know that instead of selling,
you gave everything,
you gave everything.
The brownies for free.
What's the idea?
When we motivate the brand,
we manage to have a sense of belonging,
we make people like,
validate and we can be sure that this will have much more effect
than if I had just selling the guy eating,
throwing a little paper in the trash.
turned on.
Belonging is exchanging ideas,
having history is worth it.
It's good for guys.
If you like white chocolate,
there's hazelnut,
there's edible skateboarding,
so we'll have it together,
it's great.
tamo together enjoyed.
took a while
then fabion.
I'm talking to you.
Someone who just texted me uncle eita,
you're welcome.
It's crazy.